# JOSIP MILKOVIĆ

## WEB DEVELOPER

- 00385923583984
- ✓ josip.milkovic12@gmail.com
- Put Bokanjca 43, Zadar, Croatia
- www.linkedin.com/in/josipmilković

# PROFILE

I am a talented undergraduate developer with ongoing academic education. Experience in coding web and mobile apps for displaying data. Ability to self-manage during independent projects, as well as deliver quality results as a team member.

# SKILLS

- C++
- Pvthon
- SQL
- C/C+
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

# LANGUAGES

- English
- Croatian

# EDUCATION

#### **SECONDARY SCHOOL**

Juraj Baraković Gymnasium 2011 - 2016

#### **BACHELOR OF INFORMATICS**

University of Rijeka

2020 - present

## EXPERIENCE

### APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER

Public transport web and mobile app

#### 2022

- Coding in Visual Studio Code with Quasar Framework
- Connecting to a serverless Database Firebase
- Client REST API

#### WEB PAGE DEVELOPER

BMW

#### 2021

- Website design CSS JavaScript
- Build and deployed a full functioning web page

#### **MUSICIAN**

2016 - present

• Saxophone player in a local entertainment group

#### MACHINE OPERATOR

2019 - 2020

• Operating and maintaining machine production of office materials

## COURSES

Coursera/Khan Academy/Udemy

### 2019- present

- Intro to SQL: Querying and managing data, Khan Academy
- Computer Programming, Khan Academy
- Python Django The Practical Guide, Udemy
- Blockchain Basics, Coursera